21stceg.com 2016-10-19

# Privacy Policy - 21st Century Expo Group

Last Updated 10/15/2013

21st Century Expo Group Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy. The following statement discloses the data collection and usages for http://21stceg.com. By using the 21st Century Expo Group Inc. website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

## Collection of Your Personal Information

We do not ask for or capture personal information. There is information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by 21st Century Expo Group Inc.. This information can include: Your IP address (a unique number assigned to your computer when you are browsing the internet), browser type, referring website addresses, domain names, and access times. This information is logged so that we can monitor overall traffic trends, as well as the number of visitors who access our website; it is used solely to improve the quality of the information we provide on the website, and to provide general statistics regarding the use of 21st Century Expo Group Inc.s’ website.

## Use of Cookies

The 21st Century Expo Group Inc.. website uses “cookies” to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a series of data characters that, when programmed into a website, is placed by the web server into the browser’s application folder on your computer. Once placed onto your machine, the cookie will allow the website to “recognize” you as a unique individual. Cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to potentially enhance their experience on our website. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies, if you prefer.

## Use of Your Personal Information

21st Century Expo Group Inc.. does not sell, rent or lease its customer list to third parties. We may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis. Such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to 21st Century Expo Group Inc..  
21st Century Expo Group Inc.. will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on YOUR BUSINESS or the site, or; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of 21st Century Expo Group Inc.. (including enforcing this agreement).

## Links

This website may contain links to other sites. When you leave our site to visit a third party site, the only information transferred to the third-party is the fact that you came from http://21stceg.com (the referring address). This practice allows the third-party to monitor its own web site traffic, but does not provide them with any information about you. Please be aware that 21st Century Expo Group Inc.. is not responsible or liable for the independent privacy policies of the other sites. You should consult the privacy policies at those sites to determine how your information may be used. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by http://21stceg.com.

## Changes to this Statement

21st Century Expo Group Inc.. may occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback. Those changes will be posted on this page, so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. When such changes are made, we will update the “Last Updated” date above.  
Contact Information  
If you have questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us at info@21stceg.com or at 137 National Plaza Suite #349 National Harbor MD, 20745. We can be reached by phone at 301-386-9771.
